graphtreon.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Graphtreon.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

If you choose to use Graphtreon.com, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the website. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

For a better experience, while using Graphtreon.com, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

To improve your experience on our site, we may use 'cookies'. Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the [opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Your private data**

If you have questions, corrections, or you would like delete your private personal data, please contact us.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information and we use commercially acceptable means of protecting it, but remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Our website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When you go to other websites from here, we advise you to be aware and read their privacy policy.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
